That fucking butterfly.
So what, dude! It's not my bike.
I stole it from that cunt.
That homo on Horzik Street.
The short, cross-eyed one.
Dude, I told him not to ride
on my street.
And what does he do?
He does it anyway.
So I see him coming as I'm waiting
in the bushes. Dude, I jump out...
That's my grill, cunt!
It's all bent! Do you know
how much that costs?
It's all good.
I don't feel anything.
I'm doing great!
I'm hungry.
Just as the economy
seemed to be recovering...
...we're looking at yet
another bad forecast.
Economists predict a second,
even bigger crisis...
...named 'The Black Hole',
which will mainly affect this region.
Difficult times may be ahead
for the people of Brabant.
I'll keep you informed. I'm Peter Vernhout,
reporting from's Hertogenbosch...
Look at this.
Jody Bernal's coming to Maaskantje!
Who would go and see that?
Que si, que no!
Such a homo.
Two grizzly's, noodles,
a fried sausage...
...two Ricky Martins with peanut sauce,
turkey stick, a Sloppy Joe,
...and a sausage roll,
a large order of chicken nuggets...
...and bakpaos.
Hey Henk.
You forgot my fried chicken!
- You didn't put your order in.
- I did, dude.
- No, you didn't.
- I did.
You mongoloid!
Truck driver! Honk, honk.
Hey cunt! We're done!
We got it.
Take care!
Hey Robbie, can I have one?
Are you kidding me?
I haven't eaten all day, cunt!
Seasoned meat. He likes that.
Stay away from my nuggets, cunt!
Good afternoon gentlemen.
What's going on here?
We're drinking beer.
According to regional law that is
prohibited. So hand over those beers, guys.
No.
Come on guys. Give me those beers
or I will have to take you in.
Hey dickhead!
- You feel like running?
- Excuse me?
Nice...
...it's the weekend.
Bullshit. It's Tuesday, cunt!
No dude, it's Sunday!
Fuck!
Hey! What are you doing?
- What?
- What are you doing?
Can't...
- What?
- Easy dude.
I always lift TV's like that.
No worries, dude. I bet...
...it will work when you plug it back in.
- What do you mean 'no worries'?
- No, no, no.
I swear.
I swear to you!
Hey, homo.
What you're going to do is...
You are going home.
And you're not coming back here.
What are you doing here?
Checking up on you guys.
Where are the gardening hoes?
What kind of an ugly thing is that?
That's Gradje!
Whatever.
You don't bring it to work, you idiot!
- He ruined that gardening hoe.
- Yeah. So what?
'So what? '
You know what, dude?
You and your fucking dog are fired.
And you too, Robbie.
Don't talk that way about my dog, cunt!
You can stick that job up your ass.
I'll go and get unemployment benefits.
Yeah, you cunt!
Hey, Rikkert!
You're fired, cunt.
Hey, Rikkert, just joking.
It's a joke.
Hey, Rikkert!
But you are fired.
I can only keep the best.
And I fucked your mother in the ass.
Just so you know.
Now go away, Rikkert.
Get out, Rikkert.
Say hi to your mother.
Headlines: Mass dismisssal
caused by financial crisis
I got fired today too!
Dammit! That fucking crisis!
Anyway, I think you should
start working more.
Are you crazy?
I'm already at the grocery store six days
a week. How much more could I work?
I don't know. Seven days?
What have you done in the last three
months that you've been living here?
- I haven't gotten laid. That's for sure.
- What?
What? Am I right?
We've been together for thirteen weeks.
And I'm only allowed to use my fingers.
What? Am I right?
You will have a finger, but not a cock.
It's not like you're still a virgin.
See? Nothing.
This is not working.
Call me when you're ready to fuck!
Jody Bernal is coming
to Maaskantje
- Do I smell poop?
- It's the bakpao he just had.
Can I stay here?
I got into trouble with my hoe.
Hoe!
It's all good, dude.
Dammit! That was the best part
of the show.
You are foul-mouthed.
I work, maybe you should too.
Find a new job.
I can't see.
What are you doing?
You are worthless.
You are a weak homo,
just like your father.
That's why he left you.
Dude, what are you doing?
Can I stay with you for a while?
My mom is giving me a hard time,
you know. I'll be good.
You know me.
Get off that couch!
That's my spot, dude.
Nice ottoman, right?
We are live at Gerstakker in Maaskantje,
where there's a fire.
After attempting to extinguish
the fire, the firefighters...
...had to let the home burn down.
We have no information on the tenants.
All we know is that there's
a strong cannabis smell.
I will keep you informed.
This is Peter Vernhout...
Awesome! All buds.
You can stay here too.
Sorry.
Watch me! Watch me!
I got my unemployment check.
Money for free, dude.
Let's buy stuff!
Hey.
You're not even responding.
Fine. Whatever.
That's 112 euros and 16 cents.
You said 112, right?
Yes, 112.
That's no problem.
You can make it 150.
What a bitch. She can whine...
...but she can't fuck.
What is her problem?
Let it go, dude.
Go fuck other chicks.
Maybe one without kids,
one who isn't pregnant.
I'm loving this.
Hanging out all day.
I just need to fill out the papers
for more free money.
That's what I was thinking.
Gentlemen at pump two,
please put out your cigarettes.
Thank you... for that.
Can you pay for this?
I just got work done on the car.
Of course.
That's 94 euros, please.
Get me a carton, dude.
That will be 132 euros, please.
CARD DECLINED
O, my god. What happened?
I go and buy some stuff
and my money is gone?
How much do I get from those
dickheads? I can't live like this.
Hey... Dries.
I owe you this one. We have to go.
Take care!
Social Security Office
I'm not getting enough money, dude.
I understand.
I want you to write down our names.
Richard Batsbak.
Robbie Schuurmans.
Rikkert Biemans.
Barrie Butsers.
And also include that ugly ass
Gerrie van Boven while you're at it.
Sure. And what can I do for you?
What do you think?
You need to give us more money, cunt!
Unfortunately
I won't be able to do that.
Give us more money, cunt!
'Dear Mr. R. Batsbak...
As a result of the serious threats...
...addressed to our main office...
...we need to inform you...
We need to inform you that as of
today you won't be receiving...
...unemployment benefits.
This also applies to Mr. R. Schuurmans...
...Mr. R. Biemans, Mr. B. Butsers...
...Mr. G. Van Boven.
Kind regards, Chairman of the Board.'
Goddammit!
None of us are getting any money.
If they want to play hard ball,
that's fine.
Then I won't be paying
for anything anymore!
What?
We won't be paying
for anything anymore!
Yes!
Last warning
- I don't see anything.
- Over there, dude.
Hey!
If I ever see you here again,
I will kill you, cunt!
Public Prosecutor
Chinese? Get me a Chinese
rice table for five persons.
That's 89 euros and 20 cents.
I don't have any money.
Goddammit!
- Mister Batsbak?
- Yes.
- R. Batsbak?
- All right.
You have a delinquent balance on...
Truck driver.
Ok, but...
Here's the door.
Good job, dude.
Here's some money.
Ok, thanks.
- Are you Richard Batsbak?
- Yes. So?
Mister Batsbak. Finally.
I'm with the collection agency,
and I have some bad news.
You haven't responded
to our payment reminders.
Regarding your delinquent balance.
And?
And? As a result you
now only have two days...
- I won't pay for anything anymore.
- You won't pay?
That's not how it works.
Are you deaf?
I don't have money, cunt!
And if I had it, you wouldn't get it,
you asshole!
Now, get out of here!
We can't tolerate that, sir.
We will take care of it.
It's going to be all right.
Make a left here, you said?
You, again?
Wait.
Leave me alone, dude.
You had to run to the cops.
I don't have the money,
so you can't get it from me, cunt!
Good afternoon. In Maaskantje a person
has decided to stop paying for anything.
When an officer and a bill collector
tried to change his mind...
...he made it very clear
that they were not welcome.
This is a man who refuses
to pay off his debt.
And he can't get away with that.
So I'm assuming
he hasn't been arrested?
That's correct.
But again, he won't get away with this.
If we would all behave this way,
we would have chaos.
That cop got smashed.
Look at his black eye.
Pussy!
Dickhead!
How do you deal with the situation?
I'm just doing my job.
This unusual event has shocked
the quiet town of Maaskantje.
This is Peter Vernhout,
reporting live from Maaskantje.
Hey, Henk. What about
my four bakpaos, dude?
My god. You, again?
Get your asses out of here!
My face is burned
because of you, ugly cunt!
Easy, dude.
Get your hands off Gerrie!
That's right!
Easy, dude. Just give us the food,
and put it on our tab.
You don't have a tab!
Get out, goddammit!
Easy, dude. With you AIDS-face!
Out!
Where is Rikkert?
Who is he?
This is The Dave.
Want some XTC?
- What did you say?
- Want to buy some XTC?
Some diamonds or mitsubitchis?
You're probably interested in
the old school stuff. The ones...
...that make you tweak, right?
I got those.
He's my new boyfriend.
He's from Schijndel.
Goddammit. Already?
You fucking whore!
You know what?
Two can play that game.
I'm going to fuck other girls.
No problem, dude!
Take care...
...you whore!
Such a whore!
Hi baby, are you horny?
I am so horny.
Good. I want to fuck you.
Can't we meet somewhere?
Are you in the area?
In Maaskantje?
Can't we chat for a bit? I want
to feel you inside my shaved pussy.
That's nice.
But can't you come here?
So I can fuck you,
and then you can leave.
I want you to fuck me in my ass.
Very hard and deep.
You sound like a big boy.
Oh, you're so big.
Yes, you stupid whore.
I told you to come
meet me, goddammit.
Maaskantje, close to
Den Dungen, you know.
Oh, I'm so horny.
Never mind!
You stupid whore!
Adrie, you are a police officer.
You have to show them authority.
Nobody will take us seriously.
Dickheads! Let me out of here.
I didn't rob anybody.
Joost van Gaalen again?
We have forces coming in
from Schijndel.
And we're going to get
these guys, understood?
I got it.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
We're with Brabant TV.
My name is Peter Vernhout.
And this is Rene.
Rene is our cameraman.
We were wondering if we
could ask you a few questions?
What for?
We did an interview here earlier.
You know, with your local police officer.
- How much do we get for it?
- Well, that's not how it works.
Forty euros!
That's a reasonable amount.
I think we can do that.
- A hundred euros!
- That's...
That might be too much.
I don't think...
A thousand euros!
How much money did you bring?
So... A hundred, right?
A hundred and fifty, dude!
Don't try to screw us, cunt!
I'm just a normal, hardworking...
...guy, you know.
My dog means
everything to me! Gradje.
Such a sweet dog, dude.
He needs to eat special food.
His intestines are sensitive.
But I got fired, because
I brought my dog with me to work.
But he's sick, you understand?
I can't leave him at home by himself.
That is such a sweet dog, dude.
My god, that is a sweet dog.
And because of the crisis
it's been hard to find a new job.
You could get unemployment benefits.
Dude, they don't give me
enough money.
Me too, dude.
I got fired because of the crisis.
And then I lost my wife and my kids,
because I couldn't take care of them.
And now they don't send us
our checks...
...because Richard asked
for a little bit more money.
Because he needed it to buy
special food for his dog.
That sucks, man.
Richard, Rikkert, Gerrie,
Robbie and Barrie.
Five guys without a job and without
unemployment benefits...
Are they dangerous swindlers...
...or victims of this crisis?
You decide for yourself.
Those asshole cops!
They are not going to give up.
They could come after us.
And then what?
Let them come here.
We will beat them up again,
those homos.
Hit them in the face.
I will clean that up.
Doesn't that look nice?
Richard Batsbak!
If you don't come outside within
five seconds, we will come in.
Dude!
Ten, nine...
...eight, seven...
Goddammit!
Hey, Columbo!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I don't have any money!
You can't get anything
from a man who is broke, cunt!
Stupid cunt!
I won't pay for anything anymore!
Well, ladies and gentlemen...
The police didn't make
a strong impression.
Hey, homo.
We won't pay for anything anymore either.
Hand me four more beers, dude.
Stupid cunt!
What do you want?
We were wondering
if we could...
...shoot a documentary.
It was going well.
But then officer Wanrooy...
I don't want to hear it!
Enough excuses.
Tomorrow a few colleagues from
Den Bosch will come to arrest the boys.
And you will go with them.
You could learn from them.
Are you guys fucking each other?
Homo cops!
Last night was the start of a series
of riots throughout the Brabant region.
Incidents have been reported in
Den Bosch, Eindhoven, Schijndel, Breda...
...and even Budel.
People refuse to be victims of this crisis,
and take matters into their own hands.
Yesterday, this group of guys
from Maaskantje gave the example.
Dad... I love you...
Hey cunt! Look at this.
This is crazy!
What do you mean?
Look at this fucking mess!
It's all broken, cunt!
Take it easy.
Not everything is broken.
Look at this. This is still working.
Goddammit,
you are such a stupid cunt!
You are a real bum!
Stay away from my nuggets, cunt.
Dude, what are you doing?
Goddammit, you are such a stupid cunt!
Barry! I know someone
who can give us money.
Rikkert, I'm taking the car.
I'm going to Den Bosch.
Suck my cock.
We will pay you later.
It's all good, dude.
Take care!
I want it back in two days,
plus 20 percent.
Of course, dude.
In two days you will get it back.
My promise to you. I swear.
Me and my buddies will guarantee it.
You don't have to worry.
It's going to be all right.
Go Peter!
You're number one!
Take care!
Goddammit!
Rikkert, your car!
It won't work, dude.
Look at that lock.
I got the strongest U-lock.
My car rim! Hey, cunt!
That's a good U-lock,
goddammit.
Hey!
No!
That's my Opel Manta!
Cunt!
- What do you want?
- It's Gerrie. come to Den Bosch.
Come to the Rompert Casino.
I found a solution to our problems.
Due to the delinquent
status on your account...
...your phone service
has been suspended.
We have to go somewhere.
You can wait inside.
And you better
not steal anything, dude.
Gerrie has a plan.
I'm curious to see what that is.
I lost my job, my girl
and my ride, goddammit!
How come Barrie and Gerrie
didn't take the scooter?
What?
I guess we have to walk.
Goddammit!
Sorry.
I took a shit in my jail cell,
there's shit everywhere!
Where did you get
all this money, dude?
No more bets.
Hey, cunt! Tell me where
you got all this money!
Pay attention.
Where did you get the money?
Red 23, congratulations.
Goddammit! What are the odds?
Gerrie is the man!
But he looks like an ass.
Black 11. Too bad.
Goddammit!
What a homo.
I don't get it, man.
This wasn't suppose to happen.
You are such a mongoloid.
This tastes good, dude. Coconut.
Don't worry, dude.
That guy lives all the way
in Den Bosch.
He won't come down to Maaskantje.
I don't have a job.
I lost my Opel Manta.
I lost Manuela.
She has a new boyfriend. Homo.
All I wanted was to fuck.
Just fuck, you know. Fuck.
That new guy probably
fucked her already.
What about me?
No, she won't fuck me.
Why can't I ever have sex?
For once.
Are you a virgin or something?
No.
He is still a virgin.
Hey, homo!
Homo!
Police - Confiscated
Goddammit!
Who do they think they are?
They moved quickly.
I'm going to see Manuela.
And fuck her.
Sure, dude.
Go and do that.
Make sure you get
the right hole. Virgin!
You have such a nice pussy.
I can't wait to come inside you.
Fill you up with semen.
You are such a hot chick.
Take care. See you tonight.
Hey, cunt!
...I slapped her face with my hard cock.
Like this.
She was laughing, dude.
Truck driver!
Honk, honk.
There is shit on the wall.
He didn't eat the right food.
Isn't that sad?
You want to drink something, Gradje?
You'll like that.
They cut off the water too?
Cunts!
Ground forces ready?
The warning shot means go.
What are you doing
with that bone, dude?
It tastes all right. A bit salty.
That's Gradje's bone, cunt!
Do you know how hard life is
for that dog?
They're shooting on us.
Reinout Oerlemans - Producer
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have some bad news.
We are out of money. We have
spent all the money in the budget.
I apologize. We have to cancel
the production.
We've tried everything to get more
money, but it didn't work out.
But to ensure that you won't leave
the theater feeling frustrated...
...we have decided that the boys
will tell you the rest of the story...
...so at least you know
how good the ending...
...would have been.
So boys, come over here.
There's the camera.
Good luck!
Goddammit.
Do I have to tell
the whole fucking story?
Gerrie, you tell them.
I don't think so, dude.
So...
The coppers were shooting at us!
- Coppers!
- Yes, coppers!
So we were running from them
and shook them off. Homos!
So we got to the grocery store. We saw
Rikkert's girl, she was closing the store.
She was standing there with
her naked pussy. A big one, dude!
Don't talk shit about Manuela.
What do you mean 'naked pussy'?
- I just thought she was naked.
- No, she wasn't.
So we hid there.
We thought the dog was dead.
Richard went home,
and found him still alive!
He just wouldn't die.
A true die-hard!
Such a sweet dog, dude.
You gave him a funeral, right?
A real ceremony, right?
So we were at the store.
Rikkert and Manuela were there,
she was naked again.
Dude!
What, dude?
So Rikkert fucked her like this.
Hey!
Virgin. Fuck!
Hey, did you fuck her or not?
Yes.
Virgin!
So she started whining of course.
Such a slut. She's been around.
What I meant was...
...that she should have looked
after her two kids.
Do you boys like sausages?
The next day I went outside,
and guess who I ran into, dude.
Peter Aerts! Such a homo.
He asked where his money was.
What, dude?
Where is my money, dude?
Wham, wham!
That's bullshit, dude.
You were dreaming, homo!
What were you thinking, borrowing
money from The Lumberjack?
Dude, I came up with a great plan.
To kidnap Jody Bernal!
What a homo, dude.
We had him perform anyway,
so we could steal the ticket money.
The show was in Schotsveld, you know?
I fingered llona van Zoggel there.
We ran inside. The coppers were
behind us. The place was packed.
But they started shooting.
They missed me!
Cross-eyed coppers!
So we ran outside.
We stole a car from this couple.
Rikkert got in and sat
on their baby.
Sorry.
What a stupid ass cop!
He ruined the van, killed a family...
...and lost his job.
You can stay home.
We were driving like crazy...
So we were driving.
We lost the coppers.
We shook them off.
It is him again.
I just found this in my desk.
Now get back to work! Peter?
That's a nice leather jacket!
Peter Kelder.
So we are back on.
We lost the cops!
Do you hate paying your taxes
as much as I do?
Take care! I'm out!
That was the hit show 'My name is Ronnie'.
We continue with our news headlines.
Since the start of riots in the South...
...there have been outbreaks
of violence in other regions.
Incidents have been reported
in the regions of Utrecht, Zuid-Holland...
...Gelderland and Overijssel.
It started with five guys from Maaskantje
who refuse to pay for anything anymore.
Here are Berry and Daniel
with the weather forecast.
The car is trashed!
Piece of shit.
Where is Gerrie?
He should stay far away from me.
Guys...
We should keep moving.
I'm ready.
Where are we going?
Ministry of Defence
The Hague
Leave me alone, you fucking cop!
I won't pay for anything.
What city is this?
It's actually happening throughout
the whole region of Brabant.
Who are responsible?
A few guys from Maaskant...
Maaskantje.
- From where?
- Maaskantje.
Never heard of it.
I didn't know it either. Apparently
it's south of Den Bosch.
I'm not paying. Bonfire!
Maaskant, right?
And why haven't they been arrested?
Maaskan-tje. We're not sure why.
We're unclear on the situation.
Anyway, the cops haven't
been able to arrest them.
I will throw a rock!
So if we get rid those guys from Maaskant,
everything will go back to normal?
I would think so.
Just bomb the place.
Who would remember Maaskant?
- Maaskantje.
- Right.
I had never heard of it.
I didn't know it either.
So we agree on that.
That is all?
Yes.
Oh, no.
I heard that there is still
someone out there...
...a cameraman.
But that won't be a problem.
Gerrie, that cunt!
He's acting like a child.
Such a homo.
I'm hungry.
That was big ass ball of fire!
Bam!
It hit Schijndel, cunt!
Have you ever heard of a town
called Schijndel?
Good.
Another one?
That is possible.
But it will take eight hours.
Just send our best guys, and take
them out. How many are there?
Five.
We will send fifty. That will bring
an end to this nonsense, right?
- Yes, I would think so.
- Good.
No!
Barrie!
That wasn't too bad.
Where did it go?
Look at this! Look at this!
- This is the real deal.
- Yes.
Can I see it?
You deserved that, cunt!
Where did you get this?
We don't know why the town
of Schijndel...
...was attacked.
We suspect a technical
error in Belgium...
...accidently activated a Scud missile.
Scud missile...
Scunt.
This wasn't a human error,
but a technical error.
Goddammit, this fucking camera!
I'm going to the van, I'll be right back.
Even though many people died,
there is no reason for a panic.
We have declared a state of emergency,
and have sent paramedics...
From World War II.
But they still work!
Hey, virgin!
Forget that girl, dude.
Rene, are you with me?
Are The Netherlands
and Belgium at war?
No, absolutely not.
What I've been trying to explain,
is that it was an accident.
Behind me you see the remains
of what used to be Schijndel.
I've heard from reliable sources, that
this was not caused by a technical error...
...but a failed attack on Maaskantje
ordered by the Dutch government...
...to kill five guys.
I would like to warn the people
in Maaskantje.
Leave with your families.
It's not safe here.
Craziness! Man!
This is Peter Vernhout reporting
live from Maaskantje.
Take care and good luck!
Goddammit!
They want to destroy our town?
I don't think so!
Nobody touches Maaskantje!
Can we borrow that?
Sure.
I have some more in the barn.
You can each pick one.
Those were the good old days,
the war.
This place was packed
with Jews in 1942.
You would hand them over to the Nazis
and they would give you anything.
That was a good deal.
Goebbels gave me this jacket.
Personally!
He was a nice guy.
More weapons!
Yes!
Nicky, Danny, come here!
Nicky, Danny! You'll be in trouble!
Nicky, Danny!
Hey, cunt!
Nicky?
Danny?
Thank you.
No problem.
Goddammit. Such a long drive.
Keep your hands off my croquettes.
Get out!
Can Manuela and the kids
stay here for a while?
All right. Fine.
So I take it you're not leaving?
No, dude. This food joint is my life.
I won't let anybody take it away.
Then I guess you could use this.
I am here to help you.
Craziness!
Get closer! Just aim straight, cunt!
You did good, cunt!
Hey, you fucking cop!
Let me out, you homo!
Goddammit, too much recoil!
One, two, three...
Manuela!
What are you doing here?
I got bored.
So you promise
that you will help me?
And don't act weird, okay?
Are you sure?
Gerrie!
You saved my life!
I am so proud of you. I couldn't
have asked for a better son.
- What are you talking about?
- Gerrie...
I am your father.
That is my jacket.
When you were little,
I left you with your mother.
I was way too young, and I could tell
that you were going to be a loser.
And my food joint was far more
important to me.
I was embarrassed to have
such an ugly child. But...
...you saved my life.
I'm so proud of your ugly ass. I want
everyone to know that I'm your dad.
Dad...
Son...
Do you want to have a turn?
Sure.
Cover-up?
Richard! Richard!
This one is for Gradje, cunt!
Goddammit!
Drop your weapons!
Or I will shoot your friend.
You too, mustache!
Truck driver!
Nobody touches Maaskantje!
Bang!
Fucking mongoloid!
Hey, cop!
You did that with your foot?
Cool!
Dude, where's Rikkert?
What about my boyfriend?
He is dead.
Okay.
Nice tribal.
Rikkert is no longer a virgin!
I will have to put you under arrest.
What?
Well...
Unpaid fines and stuff...
What do you think?
Please?
R. Batsbak, G. Van Boven...
...R. Biemans, B. Butsers
and R. Schuurmans...
...the defendants...
...are found guilty of the following:
Destroying private property,
disturbance of the public peace...
...public intoxication...
...drug possession...
...disrespecting an officer on duty...
...disrespecting an officer off duty,
indecent exposure...
...robbery, third degree assault...
...speeding...
...kidnapping,
destroying City property...
...extortion, tax evasion,
weapon possession, fraud...
...polluting the environment...
...unpaid parking tickets...
...withholding evidence...
...and 39 charges of
voluntary manslaughter.
The court of Den Bosch...
...sentences each one of you...
...to 240 hours of public service.
Brabant is quiet and peaceful again...
...after the instigators
got their sentences.
People have gone back to their lives,
and are coping with the damage.
Other news. Our defence minister
has not been found yet.
Do you remember me?
Stupid cunt!
You owe me money!
Shut your mouth, cunt!
I will break your neck, dude!
Try to stop me!
DJ Paul Elstak!
Don't talk about
my dog like that.
Movie theater homos!
So you you believe...
Let's start over.
Let me out of here,
homo!
Hey! Are you fucking
or something?
She's been around.
I don't feel anything.
...fucking whore.
Dammit! You ruined...
It broke.
Paul, dude.
Add some turbo, man.
No! My Opel Manta!
Fuck, that was
to the camera.
Hit her head, her cheek.
Sperm splashes
through the air.
Use the fingers.
Like a rabbit,
pussy and anus.
His mom's a whore.
I hit him in the neck.
Don't touch my cake, dude.
Look! I just found this
in my desk...
Let's do that again.
I just found this.
In my desk. So...
Fuck!
I just found this.
In my desk.
No, fuck.
That got trashed.
The court...
...of Den Bosch...
...will revoke your...
...driving license.
Truck driver. Honk, honk.