We come in peace
for cats and mice,
Everywhere.
Hey! How you doing?
Good to see you.
Thanks for coming out.
Itchy...
Itchy.
Boring!
Dad! We can't see the movie!
I can't believe we’re paying to see
something we get on TV for free!
If you ask me everybody in this
theater is a giant sucker!
Especially YOU!
The Simpsons
Movie, On the big screen!
Excuse me my hiney is dipping
Alright. Well, thanks
a lot for coming.
We've been playing
for 3 and a half hours.
Now we’d like just a minute of your time
to say something about the environment!
- Boo!
- You Suck!
- Shout up and play!
- Preachy!
We’re not being preachy.
But the pollution in your lake
is dissolving our barge.
I thought they touched
on a vital issue.
I beg to differ.
Gentlemen, its been an honor
playing with you tonight.
For the latest rock band
to die in our town...
Lord hear our prayer.
- I hate being late!
- Well I hate going!
Why can't I worship the
lord in my own way?
Like praying like hell
on my death bed.
Homer they can
hear you inside!
Relax those pious morons are too busy
talking to their phoney baloney god.
How you doing?
Peace be with you.
Pray is cheapest.
Now, today I want to try
something a little different.
I’m gonna call on one of you!
Now, the word of God dwells
within everyone.
I want you to let that word out!
Let your spirit...
What is it, Ned?
The good lord is telling me to
confess to something.
Gay, Gay, Gay, Gay,
Gay, Gay,Gay, Gay.
An immodest sense of pride
in our community.
Somebody else?
Let the lord’s light
shine upon you.
Feel the spirit.
Let it out!
Horrible! Horrible things
are going to happen!
And they’re gonna happen to you,
and you, and you,
and you!
Oh Nelly!
People of Springfield,
heed this warning:
Twisted tail!
A thousand eyes!
Trapped forever!
Dad, do something!
This book doesn’t have
any answers!
Beware! Beware!
Time is short!
"Epa"! "Epa"!
"Epa"!!!
Believe me!
Believe me!!
Thanks for listening.
- Ok, Who wants waffles?
- I do! I do! I do!
Wait a minute.
What about grandpa?
- I want syrup!
- I want strawberry!
Something happen to that man.
I’ll tell you what happened
to him.
A certain someone had a
senior moment.
But that’s ok because
we love him.
And we got a free rug
out of it.
What is the point of going to
church every Sunday,
when if someone we love has a
genuine religious experience,
we ignore it.
Right grandpa?
- I want bananas on my waffles!
- I rest my case.
I’m not dropping this.
Wait a minute! I'm still in the car!
Oh, right.
Take out hornets nest.
Check.
Fix sink hole.
Reshingle roof?!
Steady..
Steady...
Why, you little...I’ll teach you to laugh...
at something that's funny!
You know we are on the roof.
We could have some fun.
What kind of fun?
How about a dare contest?
That sounds fun!
I dare you to..
climb the TV antenna!
- Piece of cake.
- Earthquake!
Aftershock!
Ah Homer, I don’t mean to be
a nervous pervous or anything.
But if he falls, couldn’t that make
your boy parapalegirino?
- Shut up Flanders!
- Yeah, Shut up Flanders!
Well said boy!
Steady. Steady. Steady..
Hello. Sorry to bother
you on a Sunday.
But I‘m sure you as worried about the
pollution in Lake Springfield as I am.
Lake Springfield has higher
levels of mercury than even...
Why, its the little girl
who saved my cat.
Lake Springfield..
Come on over Lisa.
You can canvass me
as long as you want.
Millhouse, You don’t care
about the environment.
Hey! I am very passionate
about the planet!
Say global warming is a myth!
It's a myth!
Further study is needed!
That’s for selling out your beliefs!
Oh, poor Millhouse.
Dream coming true.
Are you aware that a leaking
faucet can waste over..
2000 Gallons a year.
- And turning off your light can save..
- ..enough energy to power Pittsburgh.
And if we just kept our
thermostats at 68 at the winter..
We’d be free from our dependency
on foreign oil in 17 years.
I’m Colin.
I haven’t seen you in school.
I just moved from Ireland.
My dad is a musician.
- Is he..?
- He’s not "Bono".
I just thought because you’re
Irish, and you care about the..
He’s not "Bono"!
Do you play?
Just piano, guitar, trumpet,
drums and bass.
He’s pure gold.
For once in your life be cool!
So, Is your name is pretty
as your face?
You ok there?
Twisted tail! A thousand eyes!
Trapped forever!!
- "Epa"! "Epa"!
- "Epa"? What could that be?
I believe it's the sound that
"Green Lantern" made
When "Sinestro" threw him
into a bath of acid.
EEEPPPAAA!
Yeah...
Thanks for coming over.
Thanks for giving me your
pregnancy pants.
I've never known
comfort like this.
Why did I...
suggest this?
Alright boy.
Time for the ultimate dare.
I dare YOU to skateboard to
"Krusty Burger" and back..
NAKED
- How naked?
- "Forth Base".
The girls might see my doodle.
Oh, I see.. Then I hereby
declare you chicken for life.
Every morning you’ll wake up to:
"Good Morning Chicken"!
At your wedding I’ll sing:
Bawk bawk bawk bawk.
Bawk bawk bawk..
Bawk?!
I like men now.
Don’t look where I'm pointing!
Stop in the name of
American squeamishness!
Boys before we eat don’t forget to
thank the lord for this bountiful..
Penis!
Bountiful penis.
Amen.
Listen kid. Nobody likes
wearing clothes in public.
But you know, It's, It's the law.
Lunch time!
You can't just leave me out here!
Don’t worry. We found a
friend for you to play with.
Nelson, Honey.
Where have you been?
- Dad!
- What seems to be the problem officers?
Tell them you dared me to do it!
If that’s true, then you should be
taking the rap here, not your son.
And...what happens to
me if its my fault?
You’ll have to attend a
one hour parenting class.
It was all his idea!
He’s out of control, I tell you!
I'm at my wit's end.
See you in court, kid.
Ok son, lets get some lunch.
- Did you al least bring my clothes?
- Shirt, socks --  everything you need.
You didn’t bring my pants!
Who am I?
"Tommy Bahama"?
This is the worst day of my life.
This is the worst day of
your life so far..
- Say Bart..
- What do you want Flanders?
If you need pants,
I carry an extra pair.
I mean..
You know how boys are always,
"Praying through the knees".
Why are you helping me?
I’m not your kid.
We’re neighbors.
I’m sure your father would do
the same for my boys.
Thank you!
- Hey, What’s with you?
- You really wanna know?
Of course I do. What kind of a
father wouldn’t care about a..
a pig wearing a hat!
Action!
Hey! Hey!
Its your old pal Krusty!
For my new pork sandwich:
"The Clogger".
If you can find a greasier sandwich,
you’re in Mexico!
And we’re clear.
Perfect.  Cut!   Print!  Kill the pig!
What? You cant kill him if
he’s wearing people clothes.
You’re coming home with me.
A thousand eyes.
What could that be?
I’m pretty sure a thousand...
is a number.
Hey Marge!
Isn’t it great being married to
someone who’s recklessly impulsive?
Actually, it's aged me horribly.
Then say hello to the newest Simpson!
Homer!
I believe what happened in church
was a warning about precisely this.
Please get rid of that pig.
Oh. You’re gonna love him!
Look, He does an
impression of you.
You nailed her.
He also does me..
You smiled! I'm off the hook.
Oh, You have so many looks.
So, that’s what snug is.
Who’s a good pig?
Who’s a good pig??
Rough day, huh son?
You don’t know what
rough is, sister.
Bart, you know...whenever my
boys bake up a batch of "frownies".
I take`em fishing.
Does your dad ever
take you fishing?
Dad, Its not fair to use a
"Bug Zapper" to catch the fish.
If you like fish like I do,
you want them to die with dignity.
I think I have a nibble.
I think fishing might
be more fun with you.
Oh Great!
Now, How about I
fix you some cocoa?
No way!
Cocoa is for wussies.
Well sir, if you change your
mind its on the window sill.
Oh my god..
Oh wait, I didn’t tell
you the best part.
He loves the environment.
Oh wait, I still didn’t
tell you the best part.
He’s got an Irish brogue.
No, No, No. Wait, Wait! I still
didn’t tell you the best part.
- He is not imaginary!
- Oh honey that’s great.
But the very best thing
is that he listens to you.
Because nothing means
more than for a man to...
How did the pig tracks
get on the ceiling?
Spider-Pig, Spider-Pig.
Does whatever a Spider-Pig does.
Can he swing,
from a web?
No, he can't. He’s a pig.
Lookout..! He is a Spider-Pig.
- Are we having fun yet?
- We are now.
- You got a bite.
- Whoa, Momma!
Oh no, my good pole!
- Oh? You're not strangling me.
- What the..?
Strangling is only good for..
Well, It's not really
good for anything.
I think the only time you
should lay hands on a boy.
Is when you’re giving him a
good old pat on the back.
Hey, What the hell are you..?
One more time.
Honey, I‘m home!
We are at the tipping
point, people.
If we don’t do
something now..
I’m sorry. I lost my
train of thought.
- Isn’t he dreamy?
- Agreed!
Ok. So here is the bottom line:
If we don’t change our ways right now,
pollution in Lake Springfield
will be at this level.
That’s not so bad.
No. The lift is stuck.
Am I getting through to anyone?
Hell yeah! We need a new
one of those things.
All in favor of a
new scissor lift, say, "Aye".
Aye!
No!
This lake is just one piece of trash
away from a toxic nightmare!
But I knew you wouldn’t listen, so I took
the liberty of pouring water from the lake
in all your drinking classes.
This is why we should
hate kids.
This is serious people.
No more dumping in the lake!
I hereby declare a
state of emergency.
"Code Black".
Black?
It's the worst color there is.
- No offence there Carl.
- Nah, I get it all the time.
Sorry. Sorry.
No dumping in the lake.
Fine. I will put my "yard trimmings"
in a car compactor.
Chief I think there was a
dead body in there.
I thought that too
until he said "yard trimmings".
You gotta learn to
listen, Lou?
Let us now make sure this
barrier is completely idiot-proof.
- Cletus!
- Yes sir.
Try to dump something in the lake.
Ok.
I can't.
I...I simply can't.
Very effective.
Don’t get any ideas!
Maybe we should kiss
just to break the tension.
- What’s going on here?
- Nothing, Nothing.
I’m not sure that pig
should be in the house.
And by the way,
What are you doing with his..?
...leavings.
Don’t worry! I devised the
most elegant solution.
- Oh its leaking!
- Its not leaking..
It's overflowing.
You filled up the whole
silo in just 2 days?
Well I helped.
Homer stop! Stop, I know its easy
for your mind to wonder...
I want you to really
concentrate on me.
I can't escape the feeling that this is
the crisis grandpa warned us about.
You have to dispose of
that waste properly.
Ok Marge.
I will.
You can take Spider-Pig with you.
He’s not Spider-Pig anymore.
He’s "Harry Plopper".
Homer.
You gotta get over here.
The health inspector just shut down the donut store,
and they’re giving out free donuts.
Oh my God, Oh my god,
Oh my God!
I just got one thing
I gotta do first.
Alright, but you better hurry.
They’re going fast.
Wow, that was close.
Evil!
Drive, Drive, Drive!
Oh, Right.
Look at that. You can see the 4
states that border Springfield.
Ohio, Nevada, Maine and Kentucky.
- Oh yeah.
- And if you look real close you can almost..
Well, this certainly seems odd, but
who am I to question the
work of the Almighty?
We thank you lord for this
mighty fine intelligent design.
Good job!
Jab, jab.
jab, jab, jab.
Hey, jab one more eye
and it's a federal crime.
- Who are you?
- Environmental Protection Agency.
Russ Cargill. Head of the EPA.
Here to see the President.
- Mr. President.
- Yeah, that is me.
Pollution in Springfield has
reached crisis levels.
I hate this job.
Everything is "crisis this" and
"end of the world" that.
Nobody opens with a joke.
I miss Danny DeVito.
You wanna joke, Ha?
Stop me if you’ve
heard this one.
Look at those angry eyes
and those giant teeth.
It's like Christmas at
the Kennedy compound.
You know sir, when you made
me head of the EPA,
you were applauded for appointing one
of the most successful men in America
to the least successful
agency in government.
And why did I take the job?
Because I'm a rich man who
wanted to give something back.
Not the money, but something!
So here's our chance to kick
some ass for Mother Earth.
I’m listening.
Well, I’ve narrowed your choices
down to 5 unthinkable options.
- Each will cause untold misery..
- I pick number 3!
You don’t even want to
read them first?
I was elected to lead,
not to read.
Number 3!
We’re being sealed in a dome.
What do I do?
I don’t know what to do.
If I stay I'm trapped!
If I leave I'm alone!
Oh god!
In? Out? In? Out?
I never saw Venice.
EPA! EPA!
Trapped forever.
Its all come true.
That crazy old man
in church was right!
Doooooooooooome!
Alright men, open fire!
Who is hurt?
Raise your hands.
Without the attitude.
People! People! I have an
important announcement!
I've just perfected an acid firing
super drill, which can cut through anything.
Yeah he is cool!
It's right there.
Just outside of the dome..
What ruthless madman
could have done this to us?
The United States Government.
My name's Russ Cargill
and I'm head of the EPA.
- The what?
- Environmental Protection Agency.
- Come again.
- Look I'm a man on a big TV.
Just listen!
- Springfield has become..
- Whoo Springfield!
..the most polluted city in
the history of the planet.
Drama queen!
To prevent your poisons
from spreading,
your government has sealed
you all within this dome.
Believe me, its the last
thing we wanted to do.
I do own the company that makes
the dome, but that's beside the point.
What? You’re telling us
we trapped like rats?
No. Rats can't be
trapped this easily.
You’re trapped like...carrots.
Wait! Wait! We couldn’t
be more polluted.
Everyone stopped
dumping in the lake.
Apparently, someone
didn’t get the message.
Act natural.
Hey buddy, sooner or later people
are gonna come by and discover this!
Don’t worry about that.
We found a way to take you off the map.
Coming up on your right..
Nothing.
This is Kent Brockman reporting to you
on a crisis so serious it has its
own name and theme music.
The dome has put an end
to life as we know it.
The town is running low on supplies
of everything from gasoline to Botox.
Moment please.
Now, as always,
we end our news
on the lighter side.
Its the time of year when the
swallows return to Springfield.
I think the thing I miss most,
is a simple summer breeze.
Maggie?!
We got: Dome wax,
Dome polish, Dome freshener.
All your dome needs and dome people. Located
at intersection 105 freeway and the dome.
"Dome Depot".
Maggie got out!
Maggie was right there.
Just outside the dome.
Marge, she’s right here.
This dome can play tricks on you.
You just have to keep calm and..
Oh my God!
I’m out of the dome!
Fresh air! Freedom!
I’ll write`ya!
Lead good lives!
Good evening this is
Kent Brockman.
Efforts to find out whose selfish
crime against the environment,
caused our entrapment
have been fruitless.
Until moments ago!
A shocking discovery has been
made here at Lake Springfield.
Ah, it can be
anybody's pig crap silo.
Homer! It was you!
You single handedly
killed this town!
I know. It's weird.
Just a reminder: This station does
not endorse vigilante justice.
Unless it gets results.
Which it will.
You didn’t listen to me
after I warned you!?
Don’t worry. Nobody
watches this stupid show.
Whats that ominous
glow in the distance?
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Marge, look! Those idiots
don’t even know where we live
Kill! Kill! Kill!
We want Homer!
Monster! You monster!!
- Did you see the news?
- Honey come on. We have bigger problems.
But im so angry!
You’re a woman.
You can hold on to it forever.
Ok.
Homer, you have to go
out there, face that mob,
- and apologize for what you did.
- I would,
but I’m afraid if I open the
door they'll take all of you.
No we wont!
We just want Homer!
Well, maybe not you.
But they'll kill grandpa!
I'm part of the mob!
Teeny, take out the baby.
Here, Let me get that for you.
Stay back! I got a chainsaw!
Bart, crawl across. Hurry!
But if they see you trying
to help us they'll kill you.
Oh pashaw! I’m sure your
father would do the same for..
Point taken.
Now  hustle your bussels!
Archers!
I’m using an red arrow,
so I know who I kill.
No, Plopper!
If you’ll push that,
daddy will die.
Hey, my luck’s beginning to turn!
Wait!
There’s something I have to get!
- What did you get?
- Our wedding video.
We have a wedding video?
Torch his gas tank!
We lost them!
Uh, Up here!
Get them! Get them!
Uh, a little help?
You know, the word "apology"
is tossed around a lot these days.
but when it comes from in here...
Mom! What are we gonna do?
Maggie, not now!
We’ll play later!
A sinkhole.
Follow me kids!
- Geronimo!
- Sacajawea!
So long, losers!
The top of his head is still showing.
Claw on it!
Well, they’re
China’s problem now.
Colin!
I can't hear you!
I never thought my life would have an
absolutely perfect moment, but this...
Lisa's got a boyfriend
that she’ll never see again!
Perfect.
What do we do?
Now, we run.
I’m afraid we lost them sir.
Well then, you find them.
And you get them back in the dome!
And to make sure
nobody else gets out,
I want roving gas squads
around the perimeter 24/7.
I want 10,000 tough guys,
and I want 10,000 soft guys
to make the tough
guys look tougher.
And here is how I want
them arranged:
Tough, Tough, Soft, Tough,
Soft, Soft, Tough, Tough,
Soft, Soft, Tough, Soft.
Sir, I’m afraid you’ve
gone mad with power.
Of course I have.
You ever try going mad without power?
Its boring!
No one listens to you.
- Bart, are you drinking whisky?
- I’m troubled.
- Bart!
- I promise I’ll stop tomorrow.
You’ll stop right now!
Come back here, Little man!
I miss Flanders.
There, I said it!
- Where’s your father?
- He went out.
Lets quickly rebuild our
lives while he’s gone.
Hey guys?
What’s the secret knock again?
Look I know I screwed up.
This is big.
Its huge! We’re homeless!
Our friends wanna kill us.
Before we can even stay
in the same room with you,
I need to know what was going through
your mind when you didn’t listen to me?
and dumped that silo in the lake.
Homer!
I don’t know what to tell you Marge.
I don’t think about things.
I respect people who do,
but..
I just try to make
the days not hurt
until I get to crawl in
next to you again.
Oh...
I mean, OH!
Look, I’m really sorry.
But I'm more than just sorry.
I’m prepared with a solution.
I’ve always been afraid that I’d screw up
our lives so badly that we need a backup plan.
And that plan is right here!
No..
Nope.
Bingo!
Stay with me.
Alaska?
Alaska!  A place where you
can't be too fat or too drunk.
Where no one says things like, "Lets
see your high school equivalency certificate."
- I don’t know Homie.
- Oh, I’m not saying it right.
Look, the thing is I can't
start a new life alone.
And I've really come to like you guys.
I just don’t see it.
Marge, in every marriage
you get one chance to say,
"I need you to do this with me."
And there is only one
answer when somebody says that..
Ok Hommie, I’m with you.
Thank you my sweetheart.
- Mom.
- Yes honey?
You just bought another load of crap
from the world’s fattest fertilizer salesman.
You’ll pay for ruining this
golden family moment!
Homer!
How we supposed to get to
Alaska without any money?
Alright son! If you don’t believe
in me, believe in America!
America! Where any man
can make quick money,
with no questions asked.
Step right up and win my truck!
All you have to do is conquer
"The Ball of Death".
- What’s the catch?
- No catch.
Just ride the motorcycle all
the way around just one time.
3 Tries for $10.
Marge, how much
money do we have?
$10.
That counts as a try.
That’s two.
And that’s three.
Tell you what I'm gonna do...
Just cause I like to see
you hurt yourself.
I’ll give you one
"On the House".
- You are the best.
- Dad!
When you’re get to the top,
don’t slow down. Speed up!
- But that’s where it's the scariest!
- Just do it!
Yes!!
Yes! Yes!
I’ll take that truck now.
Oh man...
My wives are gonna kill me.
Next stop, Alaska!
Day 37 under the dome.
We are facing
intermittent power failures which...
Ok, very funny.
Now I'm gonna turn the lights off again.
When it comes back on, I want
all my booze back the way it was.
Yeah, Ok, Ok...
I’m very proud of you Bart.
Over 24 hours sober!
- You are aren’t you?
- I’ll proove it.
Look, we’re giving your father another
chance, and we owe it to him to...
- Oh my God!
- Can I help you?
- We need diapers.
- Ok.
No...no we don’t...
ladies razor blades.
Great.
No..no..no we don’t!
I forgot! We’re European.
Just give us beef jerky.
Lots and lots of beef jerky.
That’s right. That’s what we need.
That’s all we came in for...
Sure.
Oh my God! There...
There they are!
So, you want some of my
electricity, do you?
Well, for once the rich
white man is in control.
I have two buttons
behind this desk.
One will supply your town with power.
The other releases the hounds.
Reach me.
Make me your brother.
The hospital’s generator is about
to give out.  Lives will be lost!
Lives lost.
Go on.
We got a convict we were gonna
fry tomorrow, but now we can't.
Tempting...tempting...
Look all our reasons
mean nothing..
Just look into your heart,
and you’ll find the answer.
- First door on the right.
- Thank you!
What? This isn’t the way I
pictured Alaska at all.
- Oh, That’s better.
- Homer!
Well at least my
poster didn’t get torn.
Welcome to Alaska!
Here’s a $1,000.
Well, its about time!
But why?
We pay every resident a $1,000,
to allowed the oil companies to ravage
our state's natural beauty.
- I’m home!
-Oh thanks.
- What are you doing Bart?
- Just passing the time.
Oh, my boy loves Alaska so
much he’s applauding it.
- Lisa, why aren’t you clapping?
- But dad..
Clap for Alaska!
Well Marge, we’re separated
from the kids by a wall of snow.
All my dreams are coming true.
Day 93 under the dome.
With necessities growing
dangerously low,
who knows what spark will set
off this powder keg.
Ok, Lets discuss
"Tuesdays with Maury".
Again? If we don’t get a
new book I'm going to puke.
You’re the five people I'm
gonna meet in hell!
We’re out of coffee!
I cant take another
minute in this dome!
Take that!
Oh no, blowback!
Look what they’re
doing to our dome.
- You know what that is sir?
- A crack?
Exactly.
First, let me state the problem.
People got out of the dome before,
they’re gonna get out again.
And when they do, there’s
gonna be hearings, investigations..
????????!  I’ll have to go
back to making family comedies.
Don’t worry! I have a solution for you sir.
In fact, I have 5 solutions.
You don’t even have to read them,
You’ll have deniability.
I’ll take care of everything.
You know nothing.
No!
I need to know what im approving.
Absolutely! But on the other hand,
knowing things is over rated.
Anyone can pick something
when they know what it is..
I takes real leadership to pick
something you’re clueless about.
- Ok, I pick 3.
- Try again.
- One.
- Go higher.
- 5.
- Too high.
- 3?
- You already said 3.
- 6?
- There is no 6.
- 2?
- Double it.
- 4!
- As you wish sir.
Are you tired of the
same old "Grand Canyon"?
Here we are kids,
The "Grand Canyon".
It's so old and boring.
I want a new one. Now!
Hello! I’m Tom Hanks.
The U.S Government has lost its credibility,
so its borrowing some of mine.
- Tussel my hair, Mr. Hanks.
- Sure thing, son.
Now, I’m pleased to tell you all
about the new "Grand Canyon".
Coming this weekend!
Its east of Shabbiville and
south of Capital City.
That’s where Springfield is!
Its no where near where
anything is or ever was.
This is Tom Hanks saying
if you’re going to pick
a government to trust,
why not this one?
Did you see that?
Yes, they’re going
to destroy Springfield!
But, we’re going to stop them.
Homie! Get your clothes on.
- Homie?
- I’m happy here - screw Springfield!
I cant believe you’d say
something so selfish.
Marge, those people chased
us with pitchforks and torches.
- Torches! At 4 in the afternoon!
- It was 7 at night.
It was during "Access Hollywood".
Which is on at 4 and 7.
Dad, how can you turn your back
on everyone who loved us?
Flanders helped us when
we were in trouble.
Who cares what Flanders did?
He’s not your father.
I wish he was.
You don’t mean that,
You worship me.
Oh yeah? Look what I
did to your picture.
Look at it!
Howdily doodley!
You little..
- You..I'll strangle wangle you!
- Dudley, Dudley.
Bart! Stop it!
Leave this to me.
Homer, in every marriage you
get one chance to say,
"I need you to do this with me."
That is the stupidest
thing I've ever heard.
- Homer Simpson!
- We’re saving Springfield!
Listen to me - all of you!
We are staying!
We have great life here in Alaska, and we
are never going back to America again!
I have spoken!
Well, I guess I’ve let her
worry about me long enough.
Marge? Kids?
Ok, Here it goes.
Homer, I’ve always stood up for you
when people point out your flaws.
I always say, "Well, sometimes you have to
stand back to appreciate a work of art."
Way back.
"Lately, what's keeping us together
is my ability to overlook
everything you do."
"And I overlooked these things because.."
- Because?
"Well that’s the thing. I just don’t know
how to finish that sentence anymore."
"So, I’m leaving with the kids
to help Springfield."
"And we’re never coming back."
"And to prove to myself
that this is the end..
I taped this over our wedding video."
"Goodbye Homie."
"I love you!"
Marge? Kids?
- So, Mom, What’s our plan?
- What are you doing up there?
Looking through people’s luggage..
I am the mascot of
an evil corporation.
Get down from there!
We have to keep a low profile.
Till we get to Seattle to tell the world of
the plot to destroy Springfield.
I don’t know if you guys
should be talking so loud.
No, Lisa. Its not like the government
is listening to everybody’s conversation.
Hi. I'm calling about
your meat lovers pizza.
I like meat, but I don’t know if
I'm ready to love again.
- You hang up first.
- No, you hang up first.
- Ok.
She hung up on me.
But we are fugitives
We should just lay low
till we get to Seattle.
Hey everybody! I found one!
The government actually found
someone we’re looking for!
Yeah baby, Yeah!
Homer Simpson.
Do you know why you are here?
Cause my family cares more about
other people than they do about me.
Drink this liquid.
More please.
Now, we will cleanse your spirit,
by the ancient Inuit art
of throat singing.
Throat singing?
- How long are we doing this?
- Until you have an epiphany!
Ok.
What’s an epiphany?
- Sudden realization of great truth.
- Ok
Spider-Pig, Spider-Pig.
Does what ever a Spider-Pig does.
He`s a Spider-Pig.
Unless you have an epiphany, you will
spend the reminder of your days alone.
An epiphany, epiphany, epiphany.
Bananas are an excellent
source of potassium.
Americans will never embrace soccer?
More than 2 shakes and it's
playing with yourself?
Hey! What are you doing?
Ah, do whatever you want to me.
I don’t care about myself anymore.
Because..?
Because other people are just
as important as me.
Without them, I’m nothing.
In order to save myself,
I have to save Springfield!
That’s it!
Isn’t it?
It was the most incredible
experience of my life.
And now to find my family, save
my town and drop 10 pounds!
Thank you boob lady!
This is it kids, Seattle.
Russ Cargill!
Do you think he saw us?
Yes, I did.
Run! Run!
Jump! Jump!
Land! Land!
Rest! Rest!
Run! Run!
I know we’ve had a rough day,
but im sure we can put all
this behind us and just..
It's my whipping arm!
Oh, why does everything
I whip leave me?
Must keep going..
No, I can't..
I can't keep going..
- Yes, You can!
- No I can't!
Oh, shut up! You shut up!
No you!
No you! No you!
Oh, real mature!
How can you say that?
Oh, what’s the point?
It's hopeless.
Don’t give up Homer.
You are closer than you think.
But which way do I go?
Much obliged.
Attenhut!
Lisa, knock off that racket!
Lisa!
- They captured my family.
- What do I do? What do I do?
There is something strange
about that "Sop" sign.
- Did you hear something?
- Probably just a moth.
I hope it's ok.
Look look look. We cant keep
stopping at every "Sop", "Yelled"
or "One-Vay" sign.
Just move on!
- Let us out! Let us out!
- Stop that! You’ll scratch your shackles!
I hope I do!
- Oh, way to go Bart!
- You stink!
No, you stink..
Springfield?!
I cant believe it.
But it got even crappier.
Oh, man!
Hi there, Marge.
- Moe, what happened?
- With the town sealed off from the rest of the world,
- things got a little nutty here.
- Why you dressed like that?
Well, I don’t like to brag, but I am
now the Emperor of Springfield!
- No, You’re not!
- Yes I am!
Ok..
Hail Emperor!
Attention Springfield!
Your government has realized that putting
you inside this dome was a terrible mistake.
Therefore, we're commencing with
operation "Soaring Eagle".
Yeah!
Which involves killing you all.
As I speak, we’re lowering a small but
powerful bomb onto your midst.
Despite everything,
I miss your father.
Me too. His big fat ass
could shield us all.
Attenhut!
Release!
I’m general.. "Merriot Suites".
And I have an urgent
note from the President.
Its says to release
this town immediately.
Why is it written on a leaf?
Perfect!
Now, Homer Simpson's gonna
show he has cojones! Oops...
- Mom, I’ve gotta go find Colin.
- Not now sweetie.
Doomsday is family time.
Hey, if one of us distracts Cargill,
then the rest of us can
climb up that thing.
Who’d be dumb enough to stay behind
while we escape with our lives?
My time to shine.
Hey, Mr. Big TV man, lookie here!
- What do you want?
- Look what I can do with my thumb.
You wanna know how I do it?
Four generations of inbreeding?
I can smell fresh air!
I can hear birds!
- I taste freedom!
- Excuse me, watch out, coming through!
- I was tricked by an idiot!
- Hey, I know how you feel.
I was beat in tic-tac-toe
by a chicken.
Goodbye.
Homie - do good?
Actually you doomed us all.
Again. Nice knowing you Homer.
But...
I can't do anything right!
Get out of here!
I’ve spent my entire life doing nothing
but collecting comic books.
And now there is only time to say..
Life well spent!
Ok, boys.
When you meet Jesus,
Be sure to call him Mr. Christ.
- Will Buddha be there too?
- No!
- Hey Flanders.
- Bart! How good to see ya!
- And how terrible you’re here.
- Thanks.
Listen, I was just wondering if..
before I died, I could
pretend I had a father who..
cared for me.
Come here son. There is always room
for one more in the Flanders clan.
Come on bomb disarming robot,
you’re our last hope!
Red wire? Blue wire?
Black is usually the ground.
So much pressure..
Pressure!
He’d been talking about it,
but I didn’t take him seriously.
Marge! Marge! Marge!
Oh, No!
The "Epiphatree".
Hey I tried my best.
What am I supposed to do?
And how am I supposed
to get up there?
Here, buy yourself something nice.
Homer? What the hell
are you doing now?
Risking my life to save people I hate
for reasons I don’t quite understand.
Gotta go!
First, one stop.
Bart? Son?
You think you can find it in your heart to
give your foolish old man one more chance?
I don’t know..
It seems to me, son
your father's saying he wants to
spend his last minutes with you.
No, I cant do it!
I want a father who’s the same
in the morning as he is at night.
- What’s that word?
-  Consistency!
Thanks losers.
Sorry Homer!
I’ll let you hold the bomb.
The man knows me.
I wish Homer was my father.
Well, I wish you didn’t have
the devil’s curly hair.
I’ve been taking your crap all my life!
Oh. This feels good.
No wonder you do it.
Ok, Bart. You’ve only got one shot to
throw that bomb through the hole!
Dad, in case I miss, I’m sorry I said
I wish you weren’t my father.
I don’t blame you son.
I wasn’t much of a father.
Maybe it started with the
way my dad raised me.
Yes, its clear to me.
- Its just been one long and broken cycle..
- Somebody throw the goddamn bomb!
What..
What’s going on?
No, No, No, No!
- We did it boy!
- Ah, Dad?
It's amazing no one was hurt.
Bye, everybody.
Now, that was a great
father-son activity.
Hello, Homer.
So, we meet at last.
Whoever you are.
There’s a couple of things they don’t
teach you out at "Harvard" business school.
One is how to cope with defeat.
The other is how to handle a shotgun.
I’m going to do both right now.
Wait! If you kill my dad, you’ll never
know where the treasure is buried.
What treasure?
The treasure of "Ima Wiener".
"Ima Wiener"?
- Classic.
- Well, always leave`em laughing.
Goodbye Sir.
Maggie! What a great little
accident you turned out to be.
Colin? Colin!
Lisa, Colin’s dead.
But, his last words were,
"Millhouse, take care of Lisa."
"Hold her hand".
I got her all warmed up for ya.
Colin!
Hi.
- Hey, You wanna go..
- Clean up the lake!
Well, I was gonna say
get some ice cream, but ok.
I like ice cream.
Kinda sweaty sorry.
Boy, you survived!
How?
I love you too.
Best kiss of my life.
Best kiss of your life, so far..
Steady.. steady..
steady...
Ah, dad.
Thanks, boy.
Steady...
Transcript by:
- Vdevnik
**re-edited by elstudent**
**additonal spelling fixes by Fiz**
They have taken everything sir.
Smithers, I don’t believe in suicide, but if you’d
like to try, it might cheer me up to watch.
This is Tom Hanks saying, if you see me
in person, please leave me be.
Come on dad, Lets go! I’ve been holding it
since they put the dome over the town.
You can wait. A lot of people work really hard on this
film and all they ask is for you to memorize their names.
Well, I wanna make sure no animals were
harmed during the filming of this movie.
Ok.
Whoo, floor popcorn!
Wait, Wait, Wait. It looks like
Maggie has something to say.
Oh my God! Her first word!
Sequel?